interface Question {
  question: string;
  answers: string[];
}

export const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "Name something you'd do in front of a mirror",
    answers: [
      "Brush Teeth",
      "Brush Hair",
      "Make Up",
      "Check Your Outfit",
      "Practice Dance Moves",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name something you might do when you wake up in the morning",
    answers: [
      "Checking phones",
      "Brush your teeth",
      "Make coffee",
      "Brush your hair",
      "Cleaning your room",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name a reason to celebrate a party",
    answers: [
      "Gender",
      "Graduation",
      "Birthday",
      "Wedding",
      "Bachelor/Bachelorette",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name something you keep inside your wallet",
    answers: [
      "Family/Partner Pictures",
      "Credit Cards",
      "Driver's License",
      "Money",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Things you never leave home without",
    answers: ["Phone", "Keys", "Wallet", "Credit Card"],
  },
  {
    question: "Things you would post on social media",
    answers: [
      "Coffee and Book",
      "Your Meal",
      "Vacation Pictures",
      "Selfie",
      "Pictures of Friends",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What snacks do you usually eat while watching movies?",
    answers: ["Pizza", "Candy and Chocolate", "Chips", "Popcorn"],
  },
  {
    question: "Where do kids nowadays spend most of their time?",
    answers: ["Internet", "School", "Mall", "Friend's House", "Room/bed"],
  },
  {
    question: "Name a reason you might be late for work",
    answers: [
      "Funeral",
      "Woke Up Late",
      "Bus/train Delay",
      "Traffic",
      "Sick/medical Emergency",
      "Weather",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name a part of your body that you might say has an 'ache'",
    answers: ["Tooth", "Head", "Stomach", "Back", "Muscle"],
  },
  {
    question: "Name a country with a name that starts with the letter A",
    answers: ["Afghanistan", "America", "Australia", "Albania", "Argentina"],
  },
  {
    question: "Name an espresso drink",
    answers: ["Cappuccino", "Latte", "Mocha", "Americano"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the best place for someone to study?",
    answers: ["Library", "Café", "Home", "School/Classroom"],
  },
  {
    question: "Name an outdoor activity",
    answers: ["Running", "Hiking", "Camping", "Biking", "Fishing"],
  },
  {
    question: "What are the subjects you learn at school?",
    answers: ["Maths", "English", "Sciences", "History", "Geography"],
  },
  {
    question: "Name something hot",
    answers: ["Coffee", "Tea", "Soup", "Weather", "Fire"],
  },
  {
    question: "What’s a word you would use to describe your best friend?",
    answers: ["Loyal", "Cute", "Funny", "Honest", "Kind"],
  },
  {
    question: "What are sports that are usually played by teams?",
    answers: [
      "Football/Soccer",
      "Basketball",
      "Baseball",
      "Hockey",
      "Volleyball",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name a superhero",
    answers: [
      "Superman",
      "Batman",
      "Ironman",
      "Wonder Woman",
      "Captain America",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Name things that you ride",
    answers: ["Car", "Rollercoaster", "Horse", "Bicycle", "Motorcycle"],
  },
  {
    question: "What are some popular social media apps?",
    answers: ["TikTok", "Instagram", "Twitter", "Snapchat", "Facebook"],
  },
];

export default questions;
